A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 8, Accession 8 FA1190
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Board of Directors, Committees, and Members records, 1958, 1965-2014; 11
  - Former Members: LaDier - Larson (Box 23, Folder 162)
    LaDier, Tovah, 1994-2002; Laine, Linda Noe, 1990-1991; Lall, Betty Goetz, 1966-1978; Lamm, Richard D., 1981-1986; Lamone, Rudolph P., 1984-1985; Landrigan, Philip J., 1991, 2002; Langan, Patricia A., 1982-1991 (resigned); Langlois, John D., 1975, 1998-2010; Lapidus, Gail W., 1992-1993, 2002; Larson, Arthur, 1965-1971, 1978.
  - Former Members: Lau - Lawrence (Box 23, Folder 163)
    Lau, Gordon J., 1981-1998; Lauder, Ronald S., 1982-1986; Laux, David N., 1992-2002; Lavery, Beatrice (Bee) Canterbury, 1984-2005; Lawrence, Damon, 1995-2006.
  - Former Members: Lazarus, Ralph, 1971-1985 (Box 23, Folder 164)
  - Former Members: Leavitt - Lee (Box 23, Folder 165)
    Leavitt, Thomas W., 1982-1985; Lederberg, Joshua, 1978-1985; Lee, David Fon, 1992-2006; Lee, David S., 1992; Lee, Eugene F., 1973-1976; Lee, Hong Yung, 1982; Lee, Leo Oufan, 1983-1989; Lee, T. D. (Tsung-dao), 1978-1985; Lee, Tunney F., 1981-1994.
  - Former Members: LeFrak - Lew (Box 23, Folder 166)
    LeFrak, Samuel J., 1986-1987; Lehman, Edith A. (Mrs. Herbert H.), 1966-1971; LeMelle, Tilden J., 1990-1993, 2002; Lenefsky, David, 1979-1985; Lepp, Gerald P., 1979-1992; Levene, Benjamin F., Jr., 1981-1985; Levine, Steven I., 1984-1985; Lew, Ronald S. W., 2001.
  - Former Members: Li - Lichtenthal (Box 23, Folder 167)
    Li, John J. (Jiang), 1994, 1996; Li, Victor Hao, 1972-2005; Lichtenstein, Harvey, 1980-1985; Lichtenthal, Rhoda, 1983 (Starr Foundation).
  - Former Members: Lilley, James R., 1990-2008 (Box 23, Folder 168)
  - Former Members: Lin - Lisnow (Box 23, Folder 169)
    Lin, Dinah, 1990-2002; Lindbeck, John, 1966-1970; Linowitz, Sol M., 1984-1989; Lisnow, Harmon, 2003-2004.
  - Former Members: Liss - Lord (Box 23, Folder 170)
    Liss, Henry R. and Amy C., 1982-1989; Lissy, David H., 1982-1985; Liu, Chuan Sheng, 1984-1985; Liu, Laurance C., 1978-1986; Livingston, Johnston R., 1980-1988; Loh, Wallace, 1991; Long, Charles H. and Nancy I., 1974-2002; Long, Timothy J., 2002-2003; Lord, Herbert M., 1991-2003.
  - Former Members: Lovejoy - Lowenthal (Box 24, Folder 171)
    Lovejoy, Charles Douglas, Jr., 1999-2008; Lovelace, Daniel, 1972-1974; Loving, Graham, 1982-1985; Low, Harry W., 1973-2002; Lowe, Rolland Choy, 1974-2000; Lowenthal, Abraham F., 2005.
  - Former Members: Lu - Lumpkin (Box 24, Folder 172)
    Lu Weiming, 1985; Luce, Henry, III, 1984-2005; Luck, Edward C., 1997-1998; Ludlow, Nicholas H., 1991-1994; Luk, Francis, 1982-2002; Lukermann, Barbara L., 1982-2002; Lumiansky, Robert M., 1982-1985; Lumpkin, Thomas A., 2000.
  - Former Members: Lundeen - Lynch (Box 24, Folder 173)
    Lundeen, Robert W., 1979-1990; Lutkins, LaRue R., 1979-2004; Lutnicki, Victor A., 1979-1987; Lydgate, William A., 1971, 1978; Lyle, Henrietta, 1998; Lynch, Daniel C., 2001.
  - Former Members: Ma, David T., 1979-1989 (Box 24, Folder 174)
  - Former Members: MacInnis, Donald E., 1967-1999 (Box 24, Folder 175)
    Notation on folder: Resigned.
  - Former Members: Mackay - Maloney (Box 24, Folder 176)
    Mackay, Harvey B., 1980-1985; Mackey, Cecil, 1979-1985; MacLaury, Bruce K., 1979-1985, 2002; Macmeeken, John P., 1991-2004; MacMillan, Whitney, 1998-2002, 2007; Magill, Samuel H., 1986-1990; Mahaffey, Maryann, 1995-1998, 2006 (deceased); Maloney, Sean, 2007.
  - Former Members: Mancall - Marks (Box 24, Folder 177)
    Mancall, Mark,1966-1985; Mandel, Harriet, 1992-2202; Manion, Melanie, 1992-1997; Marcus, Stanley, 1974-1985; Maremont, Arnold H., 1966-1978; Marks, E. Kenneth, 1981-1985; Marks, Edwin S., 1980-1985; Marks, Leonard H., 1972-1985.
  - Former Members: Martin - McCraw, Still Image: color snapshot trimmed to 2 x 3. (Box 24, Folder 178)
    Martin, Francis George, 1997-2002; Martin, John F., 2004; Marvel, William W., 1969-1978; Maslow, Will, 1967-1985; Mathews, David, 1988-2002; Matthews, A. Bruce, 1974-1983; Mays, Benjamin E., 1970-1978; McCarthy, James P., 1995, 2003 (Includes informal portrait photo); McClelland, Charles A., 1978-1985; McCormick, Barrett L., 1996-2003; McCoy, Tun-Hsu, 1997-2008; McCraw, Leslie G. 1994-1997.
  - McCulloch - McLemore (Box 25, Folder 179)
    McCulloch, Frank, 1972, 1978; McE1981-2005;lligott, Janet L., 1995-1997; McGiffert, David E., 1981-2005; McGrath, Lee Kimche, 1986-2002; McKee, David T., 1992-2002; McKeever, William K., 1993-2002; McKeown, M. Margaret, 2001; McLemore, Mrs. B. S. (Margaret), 1983-2000
  - McNamara, Margaret (Mrs. Robert S.), 1973-1981 (Box 25, Folder 180)
  - McNamara, Robert S., 1980-2009; Still image: 8x10 black and white print. (Box 25, Folder 181-182)
    Correspondence and clippings. Includes portrait photo.
  - Former Members: McNeil - Meyers (Box 25, Folder 183)
    McNeil, Malcolm S., 1995-1998; Meadows, Carol, 1980-1989; Mei, Kenneth T. C., 1981-1983; Mendlovitz, Saul H., 1974-1989; Menke, John R., 1976-1985; Merriam, Robert E., 1986; Mertz, LuEsther T., 1973-1985; Meyer, Alfred G., 1966-1985; Meyers, Robert L., 1980; Meyers, Robert S., 1989.
  - Former Members: Miao - Michon (Box 25, Folder 184)
    Miao, Gregory, 2002; Michael, Donald N., 1966, 1982-1985; Michael, Franz, 1968-1983; Michon, Alfred E., 1982-1989.
  - Former Members: Miller - Mitchell (Derek) (Box 25, Folder 185)
    Miller, Arnold, 1989-1997; Miller, Michael S., 1990; Miller, William F., 1984-2005; Milliken, William G., 1981-1985; Minow, Newton N., 1983-1986; Mitchell, Derek J., 2004.
  - Former Members: Mitchell, John D., 1973-1985 (Box 25, Folder 186)
  - Former Members: Mitman - Moore (Box 25, Folder 187)
    Mitman, Chuck, 2003-2004, Mohanlal, N. M. Don, 1986-1995; Montaperto, Ronald N., 1971-2001; Montero, Frank C., 1978-1984; Moore, Elizabeth Luce (Mrs. Maurice T.), 1989-1990.
  - Former Members: Morehouse, Ward, 1969-1986 (Box 25, Folder 188)
  - Former Members: Morgan - Mosk (Box 26, Folder 189)
    Morgan, Thomas R., 1996, 2002; Morris, R. K., 2003; Morse, Earl K., 1970-1973, 1978; Morton, Martha L., 2001-2002; Mosk, Stanley, 1973-2001
  - Former Members: Mott, Stewart R., 1970-1990 (Box 26, Folder 190)
  - Former Members: Mulkern - Murphy (Box 26, Folder 191)
    Mulkern, Louis J., 1971-1983; Muller, Steven, 1986-1989; Mulvenon, James, 2003-2004; Munro, Donald J., 1966, 1974-2003; Murphey, Rhoads, 1965-1985; Murphy, J. Reginald, 1974-1985.
  - Former Members: Murtaugh - Nichols (Osgood) (Box 26, Folder 192)
    Murtaugh, Michael W., 1992-2002; Myers, James T., 1970-2002; Myers, Robert J., 1983-1989; Namkung, K. A., 1994-2000; Nash, William L., 2002-2003; Nason, John W., 1968-1973; Newman, Nancy, 1986-1987; Newton, Quigg, 1967-1984; Ng, Vivien W., 1985-1986; Nichols, Osgood, 1972-1986.
  - Former Members: Nichols (Robert) - Nickum (Box 26, Folder 193)
    Nichols, Robert L., 1980-2006; Nickerson, Peter D., 1995-2004; Nickum, James, 1995-2000
  - Former Members: Niles, Henry E., and Mary-Cushing Niles, 1966-1982 (Box 26, Folder 194)
  - Former Members: Noyes - Ohrenschall (Box 26, Folder 195)
    Noyes, Christopher, 1986-1989; Odeen, Philip A., 1984-1991; Odegaard, Charles E., 1987; Ohrenschall, Robert F., 1992-1996.
  - Former Members: Oksenberg, Michel, 1969-1992 (Box 26, Folder 196-197)
  - Former Members: Oksenberg, Michel, 1993-2001 (Box 27, Folder 198)
  - Former Members: Oksenberg, Lois, 2001-2009 (Box 27, Folder 199)
  - Former Members: Olmsted - Ouyang (Box 27, Folder 200)
    Olmsted, George H., 1983-1985; O'Neil, John F. Jr., 2001-2006; O'Neill, Michael J., 1981-2005; Orleans, Leo A., 1984-1998; Ostrow, Seniel, 1966-1989; Ott, Marvin C., 1994; Ouyang, Cathy, 1993-1995, 1999.
  - Former Members: Packard - Pei (Box 27, Folder 201)
    Packard, George R., 1980-1985; Pallotti, Marianne, 1983-1987; Parish, William L., 1981-1985; Parker, Augustin H., 1966; Parker, John G., 2007-2009 (resigned); Parker, Maynard, 1974-1998; Pate, Martha Lucas (Mrs. Maurice), 1972-1977; Patton, James G., 1966-1985; Pearce, William R., 1974-1989; Pearson, Margaret, 1999; Pei, Minxin, 2000.
  - Former Members: Penaloza - Pfeiffer (Box 27, Folder 202)
    Penaloza, Philip, 1999; Perlman, Nancy D., 1984-1987 (resigned); Perry, William J., 2000; Peterson, Esther, 1973-1998; Peterson, Martha, 1976-2002; Pfeffer, Richard M., 1969-1971 (resigned); Pfeiffer, Ralph A., Jr., 1976-1986.
  - Former Members: Phelan - Phillips (Box 27, Folder 203)
    Phelan, Daniel B., 1970-1973, 1978; Phillips, Christopher H., 1973-2008; Phillips, David L., 1990; Phillips, Jordan M., 1982-1996, 2008; Phillips, Steven E., 2001-2002.
  - Former Members: Picker - Pitzer (Box 27, Folder 204)
    Picker, Harvey, and Jean Picker, 1967-1989; Pickford, Nancy T., 1985; Pikcunas, Diane, 1992-1995, 2002; Pilarski, Adam, 1987-1988; Pine, Ronald, 1978-1985; Pines, Robert H., 1981-1985; Pitzer, Kenneth S., 1971-1998.
  - Former Members: Platt - Powers (Box 27, Folder 205)
    Platt, Martha R. (Mrs. Stanley K.), 1974-1985; Pollin, Irene, 1986-1990; Polumbaum, Judy, 1988-2006; Pomerace, Josephine, 1966-1977; Poor, Robert J., 1974-1985; Potofsky, Jacob, 1967-1979; Powell, Ralph L., 1967, 1971; Powers, Brian M., 1988-1996, 2008.
  - Former Members: Prud'homme - Pyle (Box 28, Folder 206)
    Prud'homme, Hector P., 1979-2006; Pulitzer, Michael E., 1973-1985; Pusey, Nathan M., 1968-1985; Pyle, Thomas H., 2000.
  - Former Members: Quan - Ray (Box 28, Folder 207)
    Quan, Bruce, Jr., 1991-2001; Quan, Stuart H. Q., 1989-1990; Rafner, Robert S., 1999; Randolph, A. Philip, 1998 (address form only); Rawski, Evelyn S., 1978-1985; Rawski, Thomas G., 1986-2003; Ray, Robert D., 1981-1989.
  - Former Members: Reardon - Rhinesmith (Box 28, Folder 208)
    Reardon-Anderson, James, 1978-1992; Reem, Gabrielle H., 1978-2002; Reinsberg, Kurt E., Renouf, Alice, 2001; Resnick, Lynda Rae, 1996-2000; Reuther, Walter P., 1969; Reynolds, Bruce L., 1986-2007; Reynolds, Libby Holman,1969; Rhinesmith, Stephen, H., 1980-1987.
  - Former Members: Ricci - Ries (Box 28, Folder 209)
    Ricci, Louis M., 2000-2001; Rice, Donald B., 1984-1985; Rice, Edward E., 1972-1985, 2002; Riddell, Malcolm, 1995-2004; Ridgway, Rozanne L., 1992-1998; Ridings, Dorothy S., 1983-1985; Ries, Hans A., 1976-1999.
  - Former Members: Riles - Robbins (Box 28, Folder 210)
    Riles, Wilson C., 1979-1985; Riley, William B., 2004; Ring, Carlyn, 1981-1987; Ringle, William, 1993-1996; Ripley, Mary R., 1973-1991, 2002; Ripley, S. Dillon, 1974-1985; Robb, David, 1974-1976; Robbins, Charles, and Mrs. Pauline Frederick Robbins, 1976-1985.
  - Former Members: Roberts - Robinson (Richard) (Box 28, Folder 211)
    Roberts, Steven V., 1990-1991, 2002; Roberts, William E., 1966-1972, 1978; Robertson, Sanford R., 1993-2002; Robinson, David Z., 1982-1993; Robinson, Richard D., 1982-1994.
  - Former Members: Robinson, Thomas W., 1976-2006 (Box 28, Folder 212)
  - Former Members: Rocca - Rogers (Box 28, Folder 213)
    Rocca, B. T., Sr., 1965-1985; Rogel, Richard, 1993-1996; Rogers, William C., 1968-1985.
  - Former Members: Roosa, Robert V., 1966-1993 (Box 28, Folder 214)
  - Former Members: Root - Rosner (Box 29, Folder 215)
    Root, John O., 1970-1974 (resigned); Rope, William F., 1996-1999; Ropp, Paul S., 1985; Rose, David M., 1991; Rosen, Helen V., 1979-1989; Rosenberg, Robert C., 1982-2000; Rosner, Jeremy D., 1996-2002.
  - Former Members: Ross - Rostov (Box 29, Folder 216)
    Ross, Arthur, 1977-1992; Ross, Heidi A., 2001; Ross, Richard S., 1977-1985; Ross, Robert S., 1990-2000; Rossabi, Morris, 1986; Rostov, Charles I., 1973-1989; Rostov, Dorothy, 1990-2012
  - Former Members: Roth - Ruff (Box 29, Folder 217)
    Roth, William M., 1971-2002, 2006; Rozelle, Scott, 1992-2008; Ruebhausen, Oscar M., 1983-1985; Ruff, Willie H., Jr., 1982-1985
  - Former Members: Rusher - Rust (Box 29, Folder 218)
    Rusher, William A., 1967-1991; Russell, Madeleine H., 1973-1985; Rust, Edward A., 1973-1985.
  - Former Members: Rustin - Sackler (Box 29, Folder 219)
    Rustin, Bayard, 1968-1975 (resigned); Rutherford, F. James, 1981-1985; Sachs, Samuel, II, 1982-1985; Sackler, Jill (Mrs. Arthur M.), 1986-1993.
  - Former Members: Sailer, Henry P., 1973-2006 (Box 29, Folder 220)
  - Former Members: Sams - Scheuer (Box 29, Folder 221)
    Sams, James F., 1986-1990; Samuels, John S., 3rd, 1978-1989; Santos, Leonard E., 1989-1992, 2002; Saunders, Harold H., 1991; Sawyer, Granville M., 1976-1985; Saylor, Thomas R., 1982-2002; Schary, Dore, 1967-1975; Schechter, Kenneth A., 1983-1986; Schermer, Lloyd G., 1983-1985; Scheuer, Walter, 1980-1990.
  - Former Members: Schmeller - Schmoke (Box 29, Folder 222)
    Schmeller, Kurt R., 1986-1992; Schmidt, Thomas C., 1980-1985; Schmoke, Kurt L., 1988-1989.
  - Former Members: Schoyer, Penelope T., and Doreen (Mrs. B. Preston) Schoyer, 1978-2000; 2003 (Box 29, Folder 223)
  - Former Members: Schoyer, Penelope T., and Doreen (Mrs. B. Preston) Schoyer, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 223A)
    Restricted - Confidential material.
  - Former Members: Schroeder - Seawell (Box 29, Folder 224)
    Schroeder, Paul, 1988, 1993-2000; Schwartz, Benjamin I., 1974-1999; Schwilck, Gene L., 1982-1985; Scott, Hugh, 1979-1985; Scott, Robert A., 2000-2005; Seaberg, Stanley, 1974, 1978; Seaman, Bryant W., 1992-2002; Seawell, William, 1978-1982.
  - Former Members: Seibold - Senese, Processing Note: Empty folder Mrs. Eustache Seligman. (Box 30, Folder 225)
    Seibold, Frederick C., Jr., 1982-1987; Seigenthaler, John, 1968-1989; Selden, Mark, 1969-1971; Seller, Marjorie W., 1973-1989; Semmel, Andrew K., 2001-2003; Senese, Donald J., 1983-2009.
  - Former Members: Service - Seymour (Box 30, Folder 226)
    Service, John S., 1972-1975 (resigned), 1999; Seville, Marci, 2005; Seybolt, Peter J., 1973-2002; Seymour, James, 1976-1981.
  - Former Members: Shafer, Raymond P., 1981-2003; Still image: 8x10 black and white print. (Box 30, Folder 227-228)
    Includes portrait photo (folder 228).
  - Former Members: Shapiro - Sheldon (Box 30, Folder 229)
    Shapiro, Isaac, 1990-2002; Sheldon, Eleanor B., 1974-1987.
  - Former Members: Sher, Michael L., 1987-1992 (Box 30, Folder 230)
  - Former Members: Sherwood - Sidel (Box 30, Folder 231)
    Sherwood, Richard E., 1983-1985; Shouse, Jouett, 1980-1989; Shu, John, 2005-2006; Shue, Vivienne, 1978-1985; Shulman, Marshall, 1992, 2007; Siddiqui, Isi A., 2003-2004; Sidel, Mark, 1991-2006; Sidel, Ruth (Mrs. Victor), 1974-1985.
  - Former Members: Simon - Skinner (Box 30, Folder 232)
    Simon, Norton, 1971-1985; Simpson, Hoke S., 1990 (card only); Singer, Ethelda, 1983-1985; Singer, Norman, 1974-1982; Skinner, G. William, 1966-1984.
  - Former Members: Slater, Joseph E., 1972-1990 (Box 30, Folder 233)
  - Former Members: Slawson - Smooke (Box 31, Folder 234)
    Slawson, John, 1977-1978; Sloss, Louis, 1965-1985, Smith, David S., 1980-2002; Smith, H. Kerner, 1999; Smith, Joan G., 1979-1985; Smith, John Coventry, 1972-1978; Smith, Judith, 1989; Smith, Peter W., 1991-1994, 2002; Smith, Richard J., 1979-1993, 2002; Smooke, Nathan, 1978-1985; Sneider, Richard L., 1984-1986; Snyder, Scott, 2001-2002.
  - Former Members: Sobin, Julian M., 1976-2000 (Box 31, Folder 235)
  - Former Members: Soble - Soros (Box 31, Folder 236)
    Soble, Stephen M., 1981-2002; Solbert, Peter, 1966-1998; Soros, George, 1986-1989.
  - Former Members: Spaier - Speth (Box 31, Folder 237)
    Spaier, Michael, 2004; Spaulding, R. Barry, 1986-2003; Spector, Stanley, 1979-1987; Spellman, John, 1983-1988; Speltz, Paul W., 1994, 1996; Spencer, William J., 1988-2002; Speth, James Gustave, 1992-1993, 2000.
  - Former Members: Spiegel - Staats (Box 31, Folder 238)
    Spiegel, Mickey, 2000-2001; Spofford, Walter O., Jr., (deceased), 1992-1994; Sprague, Peter J., 1969-1989; Sproul, Allan, 1966-1975; Squadron, Howard M., 1979-1994, 2002; Staats, David Rich, 1995-2002; Staats, Elmer B., 1984-1993.
  - Former Members: Staheli - Steenhoven (Box 31, Folder 239)
    Staheli, Donald L., 1992-2010; Staniek, Eric T., 1981-1989; Stankard, Francis X., 1974-1985; Starr, John Bryan, 1979-2002; Stauffacher, Charles B., 1972-1989; Steenhoven, Graham, 1972-1989, 2002.
  - Former Members: Stein - Stern (Box 31, Folder 240)
    Stein, Meridee, 1983-2002; Stein, Sydney, Jr., 1970-1971; Steinbruner, John D., 1984-2002; Stepanek, James, 1991-1998; Stern, Marjorie (Mrs. Carl W.), 1978-2007; Stern, Solomon H., 1984-1996.
  - Former Members: Stevens - Stone (Box 31, Folder 241)
    Stevens, Mrs. Harley C. (Georgiana), 1973-1985; Stevenson, Earl P., 1971; Steward, W. Cecil, 1981-1989, 2002; Stone, Howard H., 1976-1985; Stone, Jeremy J., 1986-2006.
  - Former Members: Stover, Carl F., 1966-2008; Still Image: Black and white 5x7 print (folder 244) (Box 32, Folder 242-246)
    Folders 243-244 contain Stover's correspondence from his term as president of the NCUSCR, August 1971 - July 1972. Folder 244 includes unidentified black and white portrait photo.
  - Former Members: Striner - Sutz (Box 32, Folder 247)
    Striner, Herbert E., 1966, 1981-1985; Stuhler, Barbara, 1972-1985; Sullivan, Michael, 1973-1985; Sullivan, Walter, 1974-1985; Sullivan, William H., 1984-1989; Sullivan, William J., 2004; Sun, Shirley, 1975-1986; Sussman, Leonard R., 1984-1997; Sutter, Karen, 1999, 2005; Sutter, Robert G., 1992; Sutz, Richard K., 1981-1989.
  - Former Members: Swartz - Szymanski (Box 32, Folder 248)
    Swartz, Leslie, undated (card only); Swearer, Howard R., 1989-1991; Sweet, Signey, 1971-1978; Szekely, Deborah, 1979-2002; Szymanski, Christopher J., 1998-2003.
  - Former Members: Talbot, Phillips, 1972-1998 (Box 32, Folder 249)
  - Former Members: Tam - Tatum (Box 33, Folder 250)
    Tam, Wayne, 1986-1989; Tan, Chor Weng, 1980-1985; Tanenbaum, Mary M., 1978-1997; Tappan, David S., Jr., 1982-2010; Tarnoff, Peter, 1984-1993, 2002; Tatum, Donn B., 1983-1990.
  - Former Members: Taubman, A. Alfred, 1982-1989; 2002 (Box 33, Folder 251)
  - Former Members: Taubman, A. Alfred (Company Delegation to China), 1979-1981 (Box 33, Folder 252)
    The National Committee helped facilitate arrangements for the trip.
  - Former Members: Taylor, George E., 1966-1997 (Box 33, Folder 253)
    Includes critical discussions of NCUSCR's subsidy of Ping Pong delegation.
  - Former Members: Thiermann - Thompson (Box 33, Folder 254)
    Thiermann, Stephen, 1974-1982; Thomas, Frances S. (Mrs. Cecil A.), 1972-1997; Thompson, Robert S., 1983-2002; Thompson, Wallace, 1972-1985; Thompson, Wayne E., 1972-1982.
  - Former Members: Thomson, James C., Jr., 1967-2000; 2002 (Box 33, Folder 255)
  - Former Members: Thomson (John S.) - Tippett (Box 33, Folder 256)
    Thomson, John S., 1979-1999; Thornburgh, Richard L., 1983-2002; Tien, Chang-Lin, 1990, 1997; Tierney, James F., 1978-1985; Timpane, Michael P., 1986-2002; Tippett, Donald Harvey, 1967-1982.
  - Former Members: Toffler - Towner (Box 33, Folder 257)
    Toffler, Alvin, and Heidi Toffler, 1986-1989; Toll, John S., 1988-1989; Toll, Maynard, 1966-1967, 1978; Totten, George O., III, 1976-1989; Towner, Jane, 1982-1987.
  - Former Members: Townsend, James R., 1969-1974; 1980-1985; 1997 (Box 33, Folder 258)
  - Former Members: Traub - Tseng (Box 33, Folder 259)
    Traub, Marvin S., 1980-1985; Tseng, Alexander A. S., 1978-1985
  - Former Members: Tsou, Tang, 1966-1999 (Box 34, Folder 260)
  - Former Members: Tu - Vance (Box 34, Folder 261)
    Tu, Weiming, 1983-1985, 2002; Tyler, Ralph W., 1979-1989; Tyson, Ann Scott, 1995-2002; Vance, Cyrus R., 1975-1989, 2002.
  - Former Members: Vander Jag - Von Vorys (Box 34, Folder 262)
    Vander Jagt, Guy, 1996-2002; Van Patten, Anthony J., 1983-1985; Verrant, James J., 1990; Vivian, Weston E., 1967, 1976; Vollmer, Donald W., 1996-2002; Von Vorys, Karl, 1982-2002.
  - Former Members: Wagner - Walker (LeRoy) (Box 34, Folder 263)
    Wagner, Marsha L., 1986-2002; Wakeman, Frederic, Jr., 1973-1992; Walder, Andrew, 1990; Walker, LeRoy T., 1975-1985.
  - Former Members: Walker, Richard L., 1967-2003 (Box 34, Folder 264-265)
    Note on outside of folder: "Do NOT toss. Impt. NCUSCR history in Amb. Walker's letters."
  - Former Members: Wallace, John A. - Wallace, Martha Redfield (Box 34, Folder 266)
    Wallace, John A., 1974-2003, 2005; Wallace, Martha Redfield, 1975-1991.
  - Former Members: Wallach - Walsh (Box 34, Folder 267)
    Wallach, Ira D., 1973-1998, 2007; Wallach, James G., 1982-1986, 2002; Walsh, J. Richard, 1991
  - Former Members: Wang - Watt (Box 35, Folder 268)
    Wang, David I. J., 1990-1991; Wang, Jimmy, 2004 (originally filed under Jimmy Wong); Wang, John C. Y., 1978-1995; Wang, Vincent W., 2000-2001; Warnke, Paul C., 1979-1993, 2001; Wartell, Michael A., 1984-1985; Washburn, A. Michael, 1971-1978; Watson, Jack H., Jr., 1994-1997 (resigned); Watson, James L., 1999; Watson, Rubie, 1999; Watt, John R., 1990-2000.
  - Former Members: Weaver - Weitzman (Box 35, Folder 269)
    Weaver, Charles H., 1973-1985; Wegman, Myron E., 1979-1997; Weigel, Stanley A., 1974-1985; Weil, Leon J.,1992-2007, 2011; Weiss, Julian, 1994-1995, 2002; Weiss, Thomas G., 2003; Weitzman, David, 1973-1985.
  - Former Members: Welch - Westin (Box 35, Folder 270)
    Welch, Wilford H., 1971-1972, 1979-2002; Wells, Frank C., 1986-1989; Wells, Herman B, 1969-2000; Wells, Jay, 1979-1990; Wendel, William H., 1972-1985; Werner, Roy A., 1994, 2002; West, Philip, 1971-1976; Westin, Sherrie Rollins, 1999-2006.
  - Former Members: Wheeler - Whyte (Box 35, Folder 271)
    Wheeler, Douglas P., 1998; Wheeler, John K., 2002, 2007; Whitaker, Lloyd T., 1973-1989; Whitaker, Urban, 1967-1985; Whitbeck, Judith A., 1979-1985; White, Gilbert F., 1966-1970; White, Tyrene, 1988-1993, 2002; Whitman, Margaret C., 1980-2010; Whyte, Martin King, 1978-1985.
  - Former Members: Wiens - Wilhelm (Box 35, Folder 272)
    Wiens, Thomas B., 1984-1989; Wiesner, Jerome B., 1966-1989; Wilbur, C. Martin, 1972-1992; Wilcox, Bruce G., 1986; Wilcox, Francis O., 1969-1985; Wilhelm, Alfred D., Jr., 1989-1990. 2001
  - Former Members: Williams - Willkie (Box 35, Folder 273)
    Williams, Leaford C., 1973-1985; Williams, Patricia (Patty), 1993-1994; Willkie, Wendell L., II, 1999
  - Former Members: Wilson, F. Talbott, 1967-1988 (Box 35, Folder 274)
  - Former Members: Winckler - Woo (Box 35, Folder 275)
    Winckler, Edwin A., 1976-1993; Winkelman, Stanley J., 1978-1988; Winship, Thomas, 1984-1985; Wolf, Robert, 1978-1985; Wolfgang, Marvin E., 1991, 1998; Wong, Christine P. W., 1990-1994, 2007; Woo, Franklin J., 1977-1993, 2002; Woo, Margaret Y. K., 2001-2002.
  - Former Members: Woodcock, Leonard, 1971-2001 (Box 36, Folder 276)
  - Former Members: Wou - Wyeth (Box 36, Folder 277)
    Wou, Leo S., 1978-1985; Wright, Mary C., 1966-1969; Wriston, Henry M., 1970; Wu, Charles, 2000-2001; Wu, C. T. (Cheng-Tsu), 1980-1987; Wu, Chien-Shiung, 1978-1985; Wu, Tung, 1984-1989; Wyeth, Marion S., Jr., 1983-1989.
  - Former Members: Yang - Ying (Box 36, Folder 278)
    Yang, Chen-ning, 1971-1985; Yang, Winston L., 1978-2002; Yates, Michael A., 1996-2002; Yee, Frank, 1975-1987; Yee, Min S., 1973; Yhap, Veronica, 1974, 1980; Ying, James, 1980-1987, 2001.
  - Former Members: Yost - Young (Box 36, Folder 279)
    Yost, Irena O. (Mrs. Charles), 1982-2000; Yntema, Theodore, 1968-1974, 1978; Young, Charles E., 1976-1985; Young, John P., 1974-1985; Young, Nancy, 1997-2004; Young, Richard M. T., 1978-1984.
  - Former Members: Zagrzebski - Zweig (Box 36, Folder 280)
    Zagrzebski, Kelly T., 2001-2002; Zhao, Suisheng, 2003-2006; Ziegler, Charles E., 2000; Zuckerman, Mortimer B., 1992-2000; Zung, Thomas T. K., 1990; Zweig, David, 1990-2006.
  - Former Members: Baum, Richard, 1974-2009; 2012 (Box 36, Folder 281)
  - Former Members: Black, Shirley Temple, 1977-2005 (Box 36, Folder 282)
  - Former Members ( C ) (Box 36, Folder 283)